[{
    "id" : "0",
    "question": "What is the first book in the bible?",
    "options" : [
        "Exodus",
        "Genesis",
        "Matthew",
        "Revelation"
    ],
    "answer" : "Genesis"

},
{
    
    "id" : "1",
    "question": "How many days did God take to create the world?",
    "options" : [
        "Seven",
        "Five",
        "Ten",
        "Six"
    ],
    "answer" : "Six"
},
{
    
    "id" : "2",
    "question": "Where did Adam and Eve live at the beginning of the world?",
    "options" : [
        "Garden of Eden",
        "Jerusalem",
        "Heaven",
        "Babylon"
    ],
    "answer" : "Garden of Eden"
},
{
    
    "id" : "3",
    "question": "How many days did it rain when Noah was in the ark?",
    "options" : [
        "32 days",
        "40 days",
        "30 days",
        "10 days"
    ],
    "answer" : "40 days"
},
{
    
    "id" : "4",
    "question": "What did Jacob give Joseph that sparked jealousy from his siblings?",
    "options" : [
        "A special sword",
        "An arrow",
        "A coat of many colors",
        "An helmet"
    ],
    "answer" : "A coat of many colors"
},
{
    
    "id" : "5",
    "question": "Through what means did God speak to Moses in the desert?",
    "options" : [
        "A burning bush",
        "A woman",
        "A river",
        "A child"
    ],
    "answer" : "A burning bush"
},
{
    
    "id" : "6",
    "question": "What did Moses say God commanded Pharaoh to do?",
    "options" : [
        "Let his people go",
        "Feed the Israelites",
        "Pray with the Israelites",
        "Kill the people"
    ],
    "answer" : "Let my people go"
},
{
    
    "id" : "7",
    "question": "What is the name of the city where Jesus was born?",
    "options" : [
        "Jerusalem",
        "Bethlehem",
        "Cannan",
        "Egypt"
    ],
    "answer" : "Bethlehem"
},
{
    
    "id" : "8",
    "question": "Who baptised Jesus?",
    "options" : [
        "God",
        "Simon Peter",
        "Andrew",
        "John the Baptist"
    ],
    "answer" : "John the Baptist"
},
{
    
    "id" : "9",
    "question": "What did Jesus do at the Last Supper to his disciples?",
    "options" : [
        "Washed their feet",
        "Gave them money",
        "Prayed for them",
        "Gist with them"
    ],
    "answer" : "Washed their feet"
},
{
    
    "id" : "10",
    "question": " What happened after Jesus was buried in the tomb?",
    "options" : [
        "He passed away",
        "He rose again",
        "He ran away",
        "He decayed"
    ],
    "answer" : "He rose again"
},
{
    
    "id" : "11",
    "question": "How did Jesus leave Earth and go to Heaven?",
    "options" : [
        "He went in an aeroplane",
        "He rose into the clouds",
        "He disappeared",
        "He sailed"
    ],
    "answer" : "He rose into the clouds"
},
{
    
    "id" : "12",
    "question": "What day of the week did Jesus rise back to life?",
    "options" : [
        "Thursday",
        "Wednesday",
        "Monday",
        "Sunday"
    ],
    "answer" : "Sunday"
},
{
    
    "id" : "13",
    "question": "What is the 1st commandment?",
    "options" : [
        "You shall not steal",
        "You shall not lie",
        "Yous shall have no other gods before me",
        "You shall not kill"
    ],
    "answer" : "You shall have no other gods before me"
},
{
    
    "id" : "14",
    "question": "What is the last book in the bible?",
    "options" : [
        "Revelation",
        "Act",
        "Malachi",
        "Matthew"
    ],
    "answer" : "Revelation"
},
{
    
    "id" : "15",
    "question": "How did the 12 brothers get rid of Joseph?",
    "options" : [
        "Threw him in the Lion's den",
        "Sold him to slave traders",
        "Killed him",
        "Left him in the wild"
    ],
    "answer" : "Sold him to slave traders"
}
]